45cat.com 2010-11-19

# 45cat - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how 45cat.com uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. 

45cat.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

45cat.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 28th February 2009. 

**Email Address**

We collect your email address if you choose to create an account with 45cat.com 

We require this information to validate your 45cat account by sending you a confirmation email. 

We also send changed passwords to your email address when you request them. 

We will use your email address to reply to you if you choose to contact us, or if the 45cat.com team need to contact you for an issue regarding your participation on the 45cat.com website. 

We will never use your email address for any other purpose than those stated above. 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your email address with any third party unless we are required by law to do so. 

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical and electronic procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies when you use the "Login automatically each visit" option. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
